Jennifer Lemke

T: 530-209-0737 E: jklemke03@gmail.com



Summary

Experienced CAPM certified project manager and front-end web developer with a focus on user experience. Currently working towards growing my career in front-end development and searching for a related job in the greater San Luis Obispo area.

Experience

Client Solutions and UX Specialist - bLoyal

Redmond, WA — December 2014 - Current

- Manage projects for enterprise and small-medium businesses while providing consultation on best uses of the application based on their specific business needs.
- Plan and design company's web-based application with a focus on usability and customer experience.
- Create Wordpress child themes per client specifications.
- Style and skin client's web-based applications including webstores, websites, and account pages.
- Manage the deployment and implementation of our system to new clients through consultation and training of the application in a timely manner.
- Product manage new software integrations while also providing the UI interface; including a new mobile-first web based application and additions to the current platform.

Software Support Specialist - bLoyal

Redmond, WA — June 2014 - December 2014

- Resolved customer inquiries relating to technical uses of the application delivering timely and high quality incident resolution.
- Managed multiple issues, bug fixes, and questions while prioritizing resolution based on severity of issue.
- Used SQL to access client's databases to provide them with data exports, inserting in new information, and patching up incorrect fields.
- Assisted clients and development team by managing and documenting issues through the use of lab environments to conduct testing, reproduce issues, providing a technical understanding to the development team and verifying resolutions.

Education

Humboldt State University

Computer Science, BA: 2010 - 2014

CAPM Certification

Completion date: 12/24/2016

Udacity Front-End Web Developer Certification

Expected completion date: 11/23/2017

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript
- Wordpress/Woocommerce
- SQL
- Photoshop
- Google Analytics
- Invision Application
- Basecamp
- Power Bi
- Custom Report Creation
- Microsoft Visual Studios

References

Available upon request.